

NGUYEN HOANG LE AN

Fresher

- **August 28, 1996**
- Male
- 0983288043
- nhlean47@gmail.com
- 3 Thang 2 Street, District 10, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam
- i linkedin.com/in/an-nguyen-580a5 3171/

OBJECTIVES

Short-term goal: Apply my knowledge and foundation as a Pharmacists to perform assigned task, learn & understand workflow thoroughly. Long-term goal: Establish good relationships with clients and colleagues. Gain management experience and achieve a promotion.

SKILLS

English

Medical & Pharmaceutical

Communication

Office Applications



As a fresh graduate with B. Pharm degree, I've acquired the necessary knowledge for an Pharmacist. Previously, I have done some work in translation of Medical documents. Also, I've worked as an Intern at Pharmacity, which provide me consultant skills and positive attitude. Provided the skills and experiences, I'm a competent associate and I'll try my best to accomplish my assignment.



STRENGTHS

- Strong analytical skill.
- Research skill.
- Work independently.
- Persuasion skills
- Proactive



EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY OF HO CHI MINH CITY

SEP 2014 - SEP 2019

Major: Pharmacy

GPA: 7.12



WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE TRANSLATOR

JUL 2019 - NOV 2019

Translator

- Translate from English to Vietnamese various kind of documentations related to Medical and Pharmacy: news, publications, research, etc.
- Take part in translating and proofreading the SmPC and PIL for Drug registration.
- Gain experience in translating: how to avoid content error, represent infomation precisely and concisely.

PHARMACITY NOV 2018 - DEC 2018

Intern Community Pharmacist

- Learn about working manner and attitude of an professional community pharmacist.
- Assist in consulting drugs & dietary supplements, instruct patients how to use properly and effectively.
- Learn positive working attitude and how to convey the instruction and infomation effectively.



CERTIFICATIONS

Scored 965 points on TOEIC Listening & Reading test.

OCT 2019